

NUR FARISYA HANA BINTI ABDILLAH

Information Management

About Me

I am 20 years old and currently full timer student at Universiti Teknologi Mara and a part timer at a convenience store. I am very hardworking and well behave person and have desire in learning a new things.

Contact



LOT 4507,LORONG 3C,SUMBER ALAM SANCTUARY JALAN SULTAN TENGAH PETRA JAYA,9350, **KUCHING, SARAWAK**



016-6230828



farisyahana29@gmail.com



Skills

Make Waffle

•••••

•••••

•••••

Registering items

Records's description

Cataloguing and processing

Proficient using excel

Well Communication level



Education

Diploma In Information Management (University Teknologi Mara Kota Samarahan 1 Sarawak)

October 2022 - current semester

Smk Petra Jaya, Kuching

January 2017 - February 2021 SPM - 2A, 4B, 1C

Sk (A) Datuk Haji Abdul Kadir Hasan

2011 - 2016



Work Experience

Work at a convenience store as a cashier and waffle maker

2022-2024

- · Register supplier item rapidly
- Can communicate with the supplier professionally without problem

Intern at State Record Repository of Sarawak

22 July 2024 - 13 September 2024

- · Increase cataloguing and processing materials or record skills
- · Improved communication skills
- · Able to do description of document



Languages

- Malaysia
- English
- Indonesia



Reference

Academic Advisor

Abdul Ismail Haji Mohd Jawi



012-8813474